Here we go... Upokami!
This time, we're joined by Shiori Yagi of Tsubaki Factory and
and Hiko Hirayama of Angulum.
This show is about the behind-the-scenes of the production of various artists
We'll be going behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
Our recording, rehearsal, etc.
We will show you the process of our recording and rehearsal.
I've been taking dance lessons to learn how to be a theater actress.
I've always loved musicals, so I've been going to see a lot of musicals.
I have always wanted to be a part of musicals, and I had studied voice and ballet.
I have been taking dance lessons mainly in hip-hop and other genres that would be useful for Tsubaki Factory's activities.
I used to take dance lessons mainly in hip-hop and other genres that would be useful for Tsubaki Factory's activities, but recently I've been taking a lot of lessons in the musical genre with the aim of becoming a musical dancer.
I've been looking up a lot of videos and I found out that they use hats, and hats, and hats, and hats, and hats.
I've been taking a lot of lessons in the musical genre.
I've been taking a lot of lessons in the musical genre lately.
I was impressed by the wide range of dances that were performed in stage costumes, and I was also interested in trying them out myself.
I, Hirayama, am studying how to dance at festivals such as Countdown Japan.
Oh, yes, I recently participated in a festival called "Countdown Japan" with Angstrom.
I recently performed at a festival called Countdown Japan with Angulum.
I performed at a festival called "Countdown Japan" with Angulum.
The teacher who put on the sales pitch was different from usual, and he encouraged the audience in a different way than usual. I usually dance in formation, but I would break it up and sing and sing with the microphone pointed at everyone.
At festivals, there are people who don't know Angstrom, so I felt that there are many ways to stir up the crowd and to make them stop and look at the stage, so I'd like to study them. I would like to study that.
That's wonderful.
Thank you very much.
I've been doing some advanced calls as well.
I love it.
Really?
I'm called by my full name, Yagishiori.
There are different types of calls, aren't there?
Yes, there are.
I'm glad that I was able to add my own call to them.
I'm going to do it more and more from now on.
It's interesting to see more and more calls of various kinds.
I think it will be interesting to see the number of different types of calls increase in the future. Let's start with this one!
Tsubaki Factory Atarizm Vocal Recording Atarizm from Tsubaki Factory's latest album, which will be released on February 21.
Please take a look at the recording of Yumeno Kishimoto's vocals!
Start with the emero. If I raise it too high, the chorus won't stand out, so I'll try to keep it in a cool style.
I like clothes that are a little more flashy than everyone else's, nice girl, nice girl
I'm just being a little bit bossy.
I... I see.
I see. You're using a lighter voice now, which one do you like better? I'm thinking that it's not so bad now.
Let's try it with a little more of an edge, shall we?
Okay.
I like to dress a little more flashy than everyone else.
I don't mind.
It's none of my business if you think I'm bossy like that
It's none of my business.
Okay, I'll take this.
Okay, B melody number one.
Yes, please.
Please.
I guess I'm just going to shed a little bit of the first or second line here.
It's the first eye.
So...
That's where it gets exciting, the first or second line, let's make it a little bit flowing, right?
Yes.
I'm not sure if I'm good enough for you, but I'd like to believe that I'm not a replacement for anyone.
I'm not a replacement for anyone, I want to believe that.
ok, let's go to rust
ni
goo I had this, this, this, this, and if I'd just kept the rhythm
I've stood up from the lay of the land, even once the team was more than good and admitted it.
I'll never stop listening to you, I'll never stop listening to you, I'll never stop listening to you, I'll never stop listening to you, I'll never stop listening to you
I'll never stop, I'll never stop, I'll never stop.
I'm going to die
I'm going to be
I'll be able to be dead I'll be able to be dead I'll be able to be dead I'll be able to be dead I'll be able to be dead I'll be able to be dead I'll be able to be dead
If you keep the rhythm, there's the shakuroka, if you keep dancing, you'll get up
Only once after
I've only been myself once, and I want to admit it more than anyone else Listen, listen, listen, I'm the same person, there's no difference in the words, there's no difference in the place
I don't care.
It doesn't matter.
I'm not different from anyone else.
Just go with it.
You're just going along with the rhythm, and you'll become...
I'm the only one who's ever done this.
I'll tell you, I'd like to admit it
Listen, listen, listen, listen!
I can't stop the beat
I'm getting some answers
I'm starting to become me
I like it. It's hot.
The second line is a sign.
If you keep dancing, you'll become me
I'm gonna be a hot little girl.
You might as well be a shakuhachi
I've become...
Ratatta, yes.
I'll give it a try at least
I can't even take your place
I want to believe!
I've got this, I've got this, I've got this, I've got this
I'm the one who danced to the rhythm and became me.
Because I'm you once, more than anyone else
I'll say it, I'll say it, I'll say it, I'll say it
Listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me
I can't stop the beat
I'm getting some answers
I'm starting to become me
I'm starting to feel like I'm going to be me.
That's good.
Okay.
The lines... Tsubaki's famous for his lines.
Tsubaki is known for her lines.
Kishimoto didn't have many lines.
I don't. I don't.
You do have some, don't you?
Shall I take you to the station?
It's not even my first line...
It's a bit... girly.
Yes, sir.
I thought it might be nice.
Yes, I think so.
I'll give it a shot.
Let's try it.
What do you say? Absolutely.
I'll never replace anyone.
Let's give it a shot.
I'll never be able to replace anyone. I'll never be able to replace anyone.
Let's make "absolutely" a little stronger and make it "absolutely no one can take the place of absolutely no one".
I can never take the place of anyone. I can never take the place of anyone.
Okay, that's it.
That was a wonderful recording!
Powerful, Kishimoto-san!
I'm originally from the same Tsubaki Factory as you.
right?
We're recording this song.
At that time, the director told me that this song was made with your image in mind.
the director told me that this song was made with Kishimoto-san's image in mind.
The lyrics, such as "It's okay to be alone and think as you like today" and "It's fine to be alone and think as you like.
The lyrics, such as the flashy clothes, match the image of Ms. Kishimoto, don't they?
That's what the lyrics are about.
Whenever I sing, I always imagine Kishimoto-san in my mind.
So I'm very happy to be able to listen to the recording like this.
It's very helpful for me.
When you sing live, I know you're Kishimoto-san.
I realize it's you.
I can recognize you.
I can recognize you in many parts.
I think it was great to see your recording of the song.
It was great to see your recording.
You performed at Budokan, didn't you?
I was there at the Budokan.
It was very up-tempo, and the audience got really excited with it.
Tsubaki-san doesn't have that kind of fragile feeling.
I thought the lyrics were very nice, not in a fragile way, but in a strong and bright way, like "Let's be ourselves".
Like this...
I'd like to see everyone performing together more.
That's all for Tsubaki Factory
My Rhythm
This is Yumeno Kishimoto's vocal recording.
I'm sure she'll be fine as she is!
Here's the next one!
Angulum Red Line Vocal Recording
From Angulum's latest single
Redline. Here's a sneak peek of Wakana Matsumoto's vocal recording.
Let's take some pictures then, shall we?
Okay.
Okay, let's start with the en melody.
I wonder if I'm allowed to be an idiot.
Cyanide here and there.
I'll be on the next bus.
I'm going home.
It's just a little bit longer.
Dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah
Yes, ma'am.
I wonder if I'm allowed to be an idiot... cyanide everywhere
I'll be on the next bus. I just want to go home.
Okay, okay. Let's go to the next block.
I missed you so much. Really?
I'm still working on the database.
I'm still looking for a database.
Unconscious qualifier.
OK, let's go to B melody.
Oh, yeah, one more, just in case.
Unable to be frank and excited, unconsciously taking a precaution
I've been warming up, I've been worrying over it, I'm so excited about today's coordinate...
OK!
Okay, then, let's go to the torn heart...
Yes.
You may look torn, but tell me how you really feel.
What does a torn heart feel like?
Forgotten pain like that
OK, OK, that's great.
I don't know what I'll do.
No, let's stretch it out a little more.
Like that.
Stretch it once until it feels a little bit better.
Okay, okay.
Even if you look like you've done it...
Okay, then tell me.
How does a torn heart feel?
what does a forgotten pain feel like?
ok, when you get home, the rust is the rustiest part of the song...
so i did this... just now... erika... stop it... that's nonsense... i'm just doing it for you...
dry key, key, key, key!
goo love taver
This is the way to go.
I'd like to keep it that way.
I want to keep on keeping on, I want to keep on, I want to keep on, I want to keep on, I want to keep on, I want to keep on.
Tintin, talatta, talatta, talatta...
I'm trying to make the melody a little bit bouncy.
Yes?
Yes.
I'm gonna say it's for you.
I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do
I do I do I do I love you, Teibow, and I'm gonna break it
OK
Okay, let's continue.
Red Light At the sound of a show with no atmosphere I do I do I do I'll only show you Red Light
I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do
I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do
Oh, that last one is cool. I like it.
I'll take a picture of the makeup.
I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do
Let's try This kiss is proof that I'm ready to do I do I do
OK, now let's try this D-melon or something.
Well, I hope it's a little gentle.
Let's try it!
Okay, let's try it.
Innocent love, even if you put two hands on top of each other
I'm sure it won't mean anything, and I'll forget it
If you only know each other once and for all...
No matter how bad the ending is, it's wonderful, isn't it?
Yes, you've already got that melody and everything, so it's okay, it's okay.
Let's see, let's try just a little bit, just a little bit of a smile.
Yes, I'll do it.
Music
Innocent love, even if you put two hands on top of each other, it's probably meaningless, and you'll forget.
Any bad ending would be wonderful if we get to know each other's special once and for all.
OK, OK.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you very much.
Yes, Red Line is a new song, but it is the first song with 11 members, including two new members, Miyukiho Shimoita and Hana Goto, so there are many fresh voices in this song,
In the lyrics of this song, there is a red line that must not be crossed, a line that one wants to cross but cannot, or a line that one wants to cross but must not, and the song is full of such conflicting feelings,
This piece has a long solo part, and there are many solo parts. The first part is of course connected to the solo part, and the chorus is also connected to the solo part, which I think is very rare,
It has a lot of modulations,
It is one of the freshest songs in Angulum's repertoire.
I also saw Ms. Wakana Matsumoto's recording for the first time, and her voice is so beautiful and beautiful,
We usually work together and listen to each other's voices at live performances,
We usually work together, and I hear her voice together at live performances, and there are many times when we work in unison,
I have many unisons with her, but her voice is the opposite of my voice,
I have a voice that always has vibrato,
It's a different voice from mine, so it's very fresh to listen to,
I always think it's great, and it was a very cool recording.
When I first heard the song "Red Line," the atmosphere of the song changed so much,
I got the impression that the atmosphere of the song changes a lot when I heard it for the first time,
The first song has a clear A melody and chorus, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
But the B melody has a cool rap style,
And then there are some cool dance breaks.
The two of us have different choreographies,
The same choreography was done by two different choreographers, but only one choreographer, Mr. Sasaki, did it differently,
The others are the same only for the sprouts, so if you look closely, you can see people doing all kinds of moves.
It's fun.
It looks like fun.
I'd like to see it.
I'd love to see it.
And the falling rust.
Yeah, it's a bit different.
It suddenly changes and it's all piano. The atmosphere changes like a musical.
I thought it was wonderful, and the way the song ends with Sasaki-san's solo part.
I thought it was really nice. I thought it was a wonderful song because I could see all the good points of Angulum in one song.
That's all for the vocal recording of Wakana Matsumoto of Angulum Red Line.
Thanks for watching.
With Shiori Yagi of Tsubaki Factory
Yuki Hirayama from Angulum up-cami.
Here's what's next!
Juice Juice Bon Voyage: The Miracle of Thoughts Vocal Recording
From Juice Juice's latest album
Bon Voyage: The Miracle of Souls.
Okay, let's do this.
First of all, let's start with A B. There's only one line, B.
Let's go with A B.
I'm back in my favorite town, strolling with my newfound friends
The changing times made me realize where I wanted to go and my unchanging dreams.
We overcame those frustrating days together...
If I were to say something very subtle, I'd say it would be better if I could bring out a little more of the groove that the melody has.
The rest is totally fine.
The voice is great, no problem at all, but it would be nice to get a little more of that melodic groove.
That's all. Let's give it a shot!
KIMPI together
I'm getting over it.
ok, here goes the low rust
Norikoe dake dake dake
I'm fine, too
I'm fine too, my heels are falling off
I'll walk through the mud with you all
I'm not afraid of the maze 'Cause you're shining your light and pulling me along
I'll make my way through the maze
Because you gave me the light and pulled me through the maze
She was singing, "Because you gave me...
That's right.
Because you gave it to me, because you gave it to me
Cut a path through the road less traveled
Can it be a little longer here?
Yes, sir.
Okay, let's try 10,000 rounds.
If we make it through
If we get over it...
We'll get through it
No matter what the storm, no matter how swollen my heels get, even if the mud gets swollen I'll walk on with you all
I'm not afraid of the maze, the light is shining and pulling me along, so let's cut through the road less traveled
OK, let's fill in the part after the 3C dash first.
Yes, OK.
I'll do the "promise for tomorrow" and "promise to smile" later,
Okay.
So, please sing the same way as the previous sub songs.
Yes, I'll do that later.
Yes.
The end of the rainbow, I'll chase after you
Promise to you tomorrow, we'll share it all
Promise to unite our hearts in hope
I'll pile it up and turn it into a tailwind
I'm not afraid of the maze, next time I'll pull you along
Let's cut through the road without a path
I'll follow in the footsteps of my heart
I think it's a little bit difficult to sing this song because of the change in the way the words are sung,
Of course, it's important to move your ass, too,
Of course, it's important to move the ass, but I want to hear the words of "the trajectory of our thoughts," or "let's pass the story on..." or something like that.
I would like to hear the words that are to be passed on... or something like that.
Yes.
Let me say it one more time.
At the end of the rainbow, we will chase after it.
We can share everything
With one heart hoping for one thing
We will overlap and turn into a tailwind
And change it into a tailwind
I'm not afraid of the maze
I'll pull you through the next one
I'll lead the way, I'll open the way
I'll tell the story of your miracle.
Inoue-san, you were wonderful.
It was wonderful.
I had an image that this song had a lot of highs and lows.
There are so many difficult points in the song.
There are so many difficult points
But you sang it so easily.
I thought you were really cool and
I thought it was really wonderful.
When I saw your recording
I thought the transition between your back voice and your natural voice was really beautiful.
It's a part I'm not very good at.
I want to learn from you.
And the first part of the A melody...
The orchestra's melody was more prominent than the rhythm.
the melody was more prominent than the rhythm.
Mr. Taisei pointed out, or rather gave me some advice.
I added rhythm to the melody that I was singing.
I thought your technique was amazing.
I was really impressed with his technique.
He was so cool!
That's all for JuiceJuice Bon Voyage!
It was a vocal recording of Rei Inoue, the miracle of my heart!
Take care of yourself and don't overdo it!
It's time to say goodbye to Apkami, brought to you by Shiori Yagi and Yuki Hirayama!
We've seen a lot of different images this time, but for me, Hirayama, the vocal recording of Wakana Matsumoto of Red Line left a deep impression.
She is the member who sings the "D-melody" or the very calm part of the Red Line's interlude.
I could see the way she sings in her usual songs, so I was able to see how she recorded the song.
I was also able to see Matsumoto-san's sharp singing style, which is different from her usual singing style and has a stronger edge to it.
I, Yagi, was impressed by Rei Inoue's vocal recording.
Yes, sir!
Ms. Inoue has a very mature voice, doesn't she?
So cool!
I also love her mature voice.
Yes.
I thought it was really wonderful to listen to it, and I just enjoyed it.
I really enjoyed it.
I really enjoyed listening to the music, and the bureaucrats and the fakery parts of the songs were really wonderful.
Thank you very much! In Upfront Group, we're going to take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to Upfront Group.
Please subscribe to our channel and we'll introduce you to the parts you don't normally see.
This time on Apkami, we'll be talking with Shiori Yagi of Tsubaki Factory and Yuki Hirayama of Angulum.
Next time on Apkami: Morning Musume。 23 Wake Up Call Recording of Waking Up
and recording of JuiceJuice Onefull World 2023JuiceJuice version!
Enjoy!
Thank you for watching!